Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Oh...
♪ 哦...
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he. ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ If nautical nonsense be
something you wish... ♪
♪ 如果航海方面的废话是
你想要的东西...♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish. ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Ready?
SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 准备好了吗？
海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!
♪ 海绵宝宝！
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
A slow day at the Krusty Krab.
在蟹堡王度过了缓慢的一天。
Hey, Squidward, check this out.
嘿，章鱼哥，看看这个。
Two ordinary Krabby Patties,
两个普通的蟹黄饼，
but when expertly tossed
with the skill of a champ
但当熟练地抛掷时
以冠军的技巧
they become...
他们成为...
A one-way ticket to pain!
一张通往痛苦的单程票！
Huh?
啊？
Heave ho!
嗬！
What the devilfish
is going on out here?!
什么魔鬼鱼
这里发生什么事了？！
Time is money,
时间就是金钱，
and if you boys is wasting time,
then you're wasting money.
如果你们这些孩子在浪费时间
那你就是在浪费钱。
And that's just sick!
那简直就是病态！
But we were performing a ritual
to attract customers,
但我们正在执行一个仪式
为了吸引顾客，
and the only way it can work is
for us to get hurt... real bad.
唯一可行的方法是
让我们受伤……真的很糟糕。
What stupid barnacle
told you that?
什么愚蠢的藤壶
告诉你了？
Uh...
呃...
Listen, instead
of killing yourselves,
听听，代替
自杀，
I've got something real
important for you to do for me.
我有一些真实的东西
你为我做的事很重要。
Now, are you men ready
for your super...
现在，你们准备好了吗？
为了你的超级...
"Super..."
“极好的...”
Special...
特别的...
"Special..."
“特别的...”
Secret...
秘密...
"Secret..."
“秘密...”
Assignment.
任务。
Put us out of our misery.
使我们脱离痛苦。
I gotta know, I gotta know,
I gotta know.
我必须知道，我必须知道，
我必须知道。
The two of you are to paint
the inside of me house.
你们两个来画画
我家的里面。
Yay!
耶！
But, let me give
you two a warning...
但是，让我给
你们两个警告...
This here paint
is absolutely permanent.
这里画这个
是绝对永久的。
It will never come off,
它永远不会脱落，
so if I see even one drop
on anything but wall,
所以如果我看到哪怕一滴
除了墙壁以外的任何地方，
I'll have your rear ends cut off
and mounted over me fireplace!
我会把你的屁股砍掉
并安装在我的壁炉上方！
So have fun with the job.
所以享受工作的乐趣吧。
Patrick.
帕特里克.
Yeah, SpongeBob.
是的，海绵宝宝。
Mr. Krabs sure has a lot
of expensive treasures
蟹老板确实有很多
昂贵的宝藏
to drip paint on.
滴油漆。
Do you think we should take this
stuff off the walls?
你认为我们应该接受这个吗
墙上的东西？
No way, SpongeBob.
没办法，海绵宝宝。
We're not getting paid
to move stuff.
我们没有得到报酬
移动东西。
Patrick, we're not
getting paid at all.
帕特里克，我们不是
完全得到报酬。
Well, that's what I said...
嗯，我就是这么说的……
We're not getting paid,
and that's final!
我们没有得到报酬，
这就是最终的结果！
Okay, we'll just paint
around all this stuff.
好吧，我们就画画吧
围绕所有这些东西。
Good, just don't pay me.
好吧，只是不要付钱给我。
First, we need to set out
the tarp.
首先，我们需要列出
防水布。
Tarp, ahoy!
塔普，嘿！
We're going to need
more coverage, Patrick.
我们将需要
更多报道，帕特里克。
Now, that's what
I'm talking about.
现在，就是这样
我说的是。
Well, I guess we should open
好吧，我想我们应该打开
these cans of permanent
paint now.
这些罐头是永久的
现在画。
That will never, ever come off.
那永远不会脱落。
And if we get it on anything,
如果我们在任何事情上得到它，
Mr. Krabs will cut
our butts off...
蟹老板会砍
我们的屁股掉下来...
And mount them on the wall.
并将它们安装在墙上。
Careful, SpongeBob.
小心点，海绵宝宝。
SpongeBob, careful.
海绵宝宝，小心点。
Careful, SpongeBob.
小心点，海绵宝宝。
Careful, SpongeBob!
小心，海绵宝宝！
Patrick, the lid's already off.
帕特里克，盖子已经打开了。
Oh.
哦。
Now it' my turn.
现在轮到我了。
I should do this one,
too, Patrick.
我应该做这个，
还有，帕特里克。
Well, that was a rip-off.
好吧，那是一个敲竹杠。
Okay, Patrick, let's get
our brushes ready.
好吧，帕特里克，我们开始吧
我们的刷子准备好了。
Uh, maybe we should start
with a smaller brush.
呃，也许我们应该开始
用较小的刷子。
All right, Patrick,
got to get started...
好吧，帕特里克，
必须开始...
painting this wall...
画这面墙...
with the permanent paint
that we can't get on anything...
与永久性油漆
以至于我们什么也做不了……
but the wall.
但墙壁。
Well, here we go.
好吧，我们开始吧。
Just a few more seconds
of mental preparation
再过几秒钟
的心理准备
and I'll be painting this wall.
我会粉刷这面墙。
I'm getting to the painting.
我要开始画画了
Can you move it along?
你能把它移过去吗？
I'm all out of time cards.
我的考勤卡都用完了。
No problem.
没问题。
Here I go.
我来了。
Yeah.
是的。
Huh?!
啊？！
Barnacles!
藤壶！
What could be worse
than a giant paint bubble?
还有什么可能更糟
比一个巨大的油漆泡沫？
Oh, I know.
哦，我知道。
Two giant paint bubbles.
两个巨大的油漆气泡。
Patrick!
帕特里克！
Yeah, SpongeBob.
是的，海绵宝宝。
I don't think it
can get much bigger.
我不认为
可以变得更大。
Nonsense!
废话！
Pat, no!
帕特，不！
We did it.
我们做到了。
We painted the whole house,
我们把整个房子粉刷了一遍
and without getting paint
on anything but...
并且无需油漆
除了...之外的任何事情
Flopping flotsam! What's that?
漂浮的漂浮物！那是什么？
We're dead, Patrick.
我们死定了，帕特里克。
Do you know what that is?
你知道那是什么吗？
Mmm, it's a dollar.
嗯，是一美元。
I win!
我赢了！
That's not just a dollar.
这不仅仅是一美元。
It's Mr. Krabs's
first dollar,
这是蟹老板的
第一块钱，
his most prized possession.
他最珍贵的财产。
And we got paint on it!
我们在上面涂了油漆！
I think you
are overreacting,
SpongeBob.
我想你
反应过度，
海绵宝宝。
I don't see any paint.
我没有看到任何油漆。
Okay, this isn't a problem.
好吧，这不是问题。
Maybe I can just wipe it off.
也许我可以把它擦掉。
There, I think I got it.
在那里，我想我明白了。
Oh, now I see it.
哦，现在我明白了。
This is not good, Patrick.
这不好，帕特里克。
This is not good.
这不好。
Mr. Krabs is going
to be home soon,
蟹老板要走了
很快就能回家，
and when he sees what we did
to his dollar...
当他看到我们所做的事情时
到他的美元...
Wait, SpongeBob, all we got
to do is wash the paint off
等等，海绵宝宝，我们只剩下一切了
要做的就是把油漆洗掉
and Krabs will never know.
蟹蟹永远不会知道。
But Mr. Krabs said...
但蟹老板说……
Forget what
Mr. Krabs said.
忘了什么
蟹老板说道。
Every paint comes off
with something.
每个油漆都会脱落
与某事。
Did it work?
有效吗？
No.
不。
Did it work?
有效吗？
No.
不。
Did it work?
有效吗？
No.
不。
Nothing's working!
什么都不起作用！
Wait, SpongeBob!
等等，海绵宝宝！
We're not cavemen.
我们不是穴居人。
We have technology.
我们有技术。
It didn't work.
它不起作用。
This is all Mr. Krabs' fault.
这都是蟹老板的错。
If he hadn't hung that stupid
dollar in the first place...
如果他没有那么傻的话
首先美元...
I mean, it's not like
it looks any different
我的意思是，这不像
它看起来有什么不同
than a regular dollar.
比普通美元。
Why hang it?
为什么要挂它？
You could just stick any old
dollar bill up on the wall...
你可以只粘任何旧的
墙上挂着一美元的钞票...
No one would even
know the difference.
甚至没有人会
知道其中的区别。
You might as well just reach
into my wallet,
你也可以直接到达
进我的钱包，
pull out a dollar
and put it on the wall.
拿出一美元
并把它贴在墙上。
Okay, Patrick,
take out your wallet.
好吧，帕特里克，
拿出你的钱包。
I don't see where
you're going with this.
我不知道在哪里
你就这样吧。
Hey, a dollar.
嘿，一美元。
Our butts are saved, Patrick.
我们的屁股有救了，帕特里克。
Now all we have to...
现在我们所要做的就是...
Patrick, no!
帕特里克，不！
Patrick, no.
帕特里克，不。
Why did you put it...?
为什么你把它...？
Grab it, Pat, grab it.
抓住它，帕特，抓住它。
Hurry, hurry!
快点，快点！
Oh, Pat, no, no.
哦，帕特，不，不。
Get it, Pat, get it,
get it, get it.
得到它，帕特，得到它，
得到它，得到它。
Want a bite?
想咬一口吗？
Okay, okay, we still got time.
好吧好吧，我们还有时间。
Don't panic, SpongeBob,
panic is the enemy.
别惊慌，海绵宝宝，
恐慌是敌人。
You are strong.
你很坚强。
Through your strength
you shall overcome.
通过你的力量
你一定会克服的。
You're on your own, pal.
你只能靠自己了，朋友。
Hurry, Patrick, put the dollar
back on the wall.
快点，帕特里克，把美元放进去
回到墙上。
I got an idea.
我有一个主意。
♪ La, la, la-la-la.
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦。
What the...?
什么……？
We're all done.
我们都完成了。
Everything looks great.
一切看起来都很棒。
Yeah, you don't
have to look around.
是的，你不
必须环顾四周。
We already did that for you.
我们已经为您做到了。
You both look like you got
你们俩看起来都像
a dirty little secret.
一个肮脏的小秘密。
Ha, I'm kidding.
哈，我开玩笑的。
Let's see how you did.
让我们看看你是怎么做的。
Ooh, not bad, boys, not bad.
哦，不错，孩子们，不错。
A nice even coat,
high gloss, no bubbles.
一件漂亮均匀的外套，
高光泽、无气泡。
Yeah, looks great, Mr. Krabs.
是的，看起来很棒，蟹老板。
We'll just be going.
我们就走吧。
Flipping fish parcels,
look what you did!
翻转鱼包，
看看你做了什么！
Please don't cut off our butts.
请不要砍掉我们的屁股。
Oh, Mr. Krabs,
I'm so sorry.
哦，蟹老板，
我很抱歉。
"Sorry?"
“对不起？”
You dusted all my knickknacks.
你把我所有的小玩意儿都掸掉了。
That was really nice.
那真是太好了。
Great Barrier Reef!
大堡礁！
What's this?
这是什么？
That's not our fault.
那不是我们的错。
I don't want to be buttless.
我不想成为无屁股的人。
Oh, and I suppose
the floor molding
哦，我想
地板造型
just painted itself on its own.
只是自己画了自己。
That's what I call
craftsmanship.
这就是我所说的
工艺。
Criminy jim jim!
犯罪的吉姆吉姆！
You messed up my dollar...
你弄乱了我的美元...
rama.
罗摩。
All the dolls in this dollarama
这个美元娃娃里的所有娃娃
were perfectly aligned.
完全一致。
Mama.
妈妈。
And you boys thought
I wouldn't notice.
你们男孩以为
我不会注意到。
Oh, well, I guess no harm done.
哦，好吧，我想没有造成任何伤害。
All right, boys,
好吧，孩子们，
you're free to go.
你可以走了。
Ow! That's funny.
噢！那很好笑。
I don't remember
a stack of paintings
我不记得了
一摞画
where me first dollar
used to be.
我的第一块钱在哪里
曾经是。
In fact, I don't remember
this painting at all.
其实我不记得了
这幅画根本就没有。
Or this one.
或者这个。
Hi, Mr. Krabs.
嗨，蟹老板。
SpongeBob, what are you doing?
海绵宝宝，你在做什么？
Oh, you know,
just hanging around.
哦，你知道，
只是闲逛。
Boo!
嘘！
Get down onto the floor, boy.
趴到地上吧，孩子。
All right, now you're
just being silly.
好吧，现在你
只是很傻。
No, no, no!
不，不，不！
Mr. Krabs, no.
蟹老板先生，不。
Don't look.
别看。
It's a trick.
这是一个诡计。
Did you two get paint
all over me first dollar?!
你们两个有油漆吗
都在我的第一美元？！
We're so sorry,
Mr. Krabs.
我们非常抱歉，
蟹老板。
And then did you
draw on it with crayon?
然后你有没有
用蜡笔在上面画画？
I thought, you know,
maybe he'd buy it.
我想，你知道，
也许他会买。
All right, boys!
好吧，孩子们！
You know what I've got
to do now?
你知道我有什么
现在做什么？
You mean, our butts?
你是说我们的屁股？
Can I use mine one last time?
我可以用我的最后一次吗？
There we go, good as new.
就这样，一切如新。
But... but... but... but...
但是……但是……但是……但是……
Yeah, I lied.
是的，我撒谎了。
This paint actually
comes off with saliva.
这个漆其实
随唾液脱落。
Oh, I get it, Mr. Krabs.
哦，我明白了，蟹老板。
You told us the paint
was permanent
你告诉我们油漆
是永久的
so me and Patrick
would be more careful
所以我和帕特里克
会更加小心
and not get paint on anything.
并且不要在任何东西上涂漆。
Nah, I just like
to mess with you.
嗯，我只是喜欢
来惹你。
Oh, the old man's still got it.
唉，老子还是懂的。
Aw, crud.
噢，粗俗。
I really got to learn to say it,
not spray it.
我真的要学会说
不喷它。
Welcome aboard.
欢迎登机。
If you're watching this video,
then let me be the first to say:
如果你正在看这个视频，
那么我首先要说的是：
You've recently been hired
您最近被录用了
by The Krusty Krab Restaurant
由蟹堡王餐厅提供
and this is your first official
day of training.
这是你的第一个官方
训练日。
Can I make a Krabby Patty now?
我现在可以做蟹黄饼吗？
Oh, no, you've got
a lot to learn
哦，不，你有
有很多东西要学
before you're ready
to make a Krabby Patty.
在你准备好之前
制作蟹黄饼。
As you can see by this graph...
正如您通过该图所看到的...
Graph.
图形。
You are now employed
您现在已就业
by one of the most successful
restaurants in Bikini Bottom.
由最成功的人之一
比基尼堡的餐馆。
But it didn't get that way
overnight...
但事实并非如此
一夜之间...
because the store closes
at 6:00.
因为商店关门了
6:00。
No, story of The Krusty Krab
不，是蟹堡王的故事
is a story of one man's hard
work, perseverance, vision,
是一个男人艰难的故事
工作、毅力、愿景、
determination and sweat.
决心和汗水。
But mostly his sweat.
但主要是他的汗水。
You may think
Mr. Eugene H. Krabs,
你可能会想
尊敬的尤金·克拉布斯先生，
owner and founder
of Krusty Krab Inc.,
所有者和创始人
蟹堡王公司，
has always been the financial
wizard he is today.
一直是金融
今天的他就是巫师。
And you're right.
你是对的。
After the war,
战争结束后，
Krabs stayed secluded in a deep
depression that seemed endless.
螃蟹们躲在深处
抑郁似乎永无休止。
But then his luck changed
但后来他的运气发生了变化
when he acquired a bankrupt
retirement home,
当他收购破产者时
养老院、
and with a few minor
alterations,
以及一些小事
改动，
The Krusty Krab was born.
蟹堡王诞生了。
Sounds like a lot of...
听起来好像很多...
Hoopla!
呼啦啦！
Sounds like a lot...
听起来好像很多...
Hoopla!
呼啦啦！
Sounds like a...
听起来像是一个...
Hoopla!
呼啦啦！
Sounds like a lot of hoopla
听起来有很多喧嚣
to make over
a little Krabby Patty, right?
改过自新
有点蟹蟹派蒂，对吧？
Wrong!
错误的！
To keep up with today's
demanding customers,
为了跟上今天的步伐
要求严格的客户，
no expense has been spared
不遗余力
to acquire
all the latest achievements
获得
所有最新成就
in fast-food technology.
在快餐技术方面。
This here is an advanced
patty-control mechanism.
这是一个高级的
肉饼控制机制。
Here you see our automated
money-handling system.
在这里您可以看到我们的自动化
货币处理系统。
Don't touch.
别碰。
These are high-quality
这些都是高品质的
beverage temperature devices.
饮料温度装置。
Imported.
进口的。
This here's a prototype
liquid transfer machine.
这是一个原型
液体转移机。
And most importantly,
最重要的是，
you get your state-of-the-art
你得到最先进的
condiment-dispersal units.
调味品分散装置。
You going to buy something?
你要买东西吗？
There's a standing fee.
有固定费用。
All of this modernization
所有这些现代化
seems a little overwhelming
doesn't it?
似乎有点势不可挡
不是吗？
Well, luckily for you,
嗯，你很幸运，
Mr. Krabs' fear
of robot overlords
蟹老板的恐惧
机器人霸主
keeps the balance of technology
in check.
保持技术的平衡
在检查中。
But if modernization
is the heart of The Krusty Krab,
但如果现代化
是蟹堡王的核心，
then employees
are the liver and gallbladder.
然后是员工
是肝脏和胆囊。
Let's see
if you've got what it takes.
让我们看看
如果你有能力的话。
Hmm... poised, confident,
and a smile that says,
嗯……沉着、自信、
和一个微笑说，
"Hello, world,
may I take your order?"
“你好，世界，
我可以接受您的命令吗？”
You've got the makings of a
good employee, Mr. SquarePants.
你已经具备了成为一名
好员工，方裤先生。
But for every good employee,
there's one who is not so good.
但对于每一个优秀的员工来说，
有一个人不太好。
Let's see...
inattentive, impatient,
让我们看看...
不专心、不耐烦、
a glazed look in the eyes.
眼神呆滞。
Look carefully
仔细看
at the, "I Really Wish I Weren't
Here Right Now" button.
在“我真的希望我不是
现在就在这里”按钮。
There's a name
for employees like this,
有一个名字
对于这样的员工来说，
but we'll call him Squidward.
但我们会叫他章鱼哥。
I'm getting paid overtime
for this, right, Mr. Krabs?
我有加班费
为了这个，对吧，蟹老板？
Sorry, can't hear you!
抱歉，听不到你的声音！
Does this mean I get to
make a Krabby Patty now?
这是否意味着我可以
现在做蟹黄饼吗？
No, you can't
make a Krabby Patty
不，你不能
做一个蟹肉饼
without understanding
the phrase:
不理解
短语：
"POOP"?
“船尾”？
Once you understand POOP,
一旦你了解了便便，
you'll understand your place
at The Krusty Krab.
你会明白你的位置
在蟹堡王。
But what does POOP mean?
但便便是什么意思呢？
It's actually
a carefully organized code.
其实是
精心组织的代码。
Watch closely.
仔细观察。
Ah... POOP!
啊...便便！
Looks like Mr. SquarePants
understands POOP.
看起来像方裤先生
了解便便。
Here's a typical customer.
这是一个典型的客户。
I wonder what he wants.
我想知道他想要什么。
Well, if we just remember POOP,
we can figure it out.
好吧，如果我们只记得便便，
我们可以弄清楚。
I'd like to order...
我想要奌菜...
Do you think
he's going to order:
你认为
他要订购：
One patty, please.
请给我一份肉饼。
Ah, POOP, you never let us down!
啊，POOP，你从来没有让我们失望过！
Now that you understand POOP,
现在您了解了便便，
I bet you think you're ready
to make a Krabby Patty.
我打赌你认为你已经准备好了
制作蟹黄饼。
Krabby Patty!
蟹蟹帕蒂！
Ha-ha... not so fast,
Eager McBeaver.
哈哈……没这么快吧
热切的麦克比弗。
We haven't even talked about:
我们甚至还没有讨论过：
Every employee
of The Krusty Krab
每一位员工
蟹堡王的
must comply with a strict set
of personal hygiene guidelines.
必须遵守严格的规定
个人卫生指南。
Okay, Mr. SquarePants,
好的，方裤先生，
are you ready to prepare
for your shift?
你准备好了吗
值班吗？
A good employee always
scrubs his hands thoroughly.
永远是好员工
彻底擦洗双手。
Be sure to get under
those fingernails.
一定要下
那些指甲。
And don't forget
about the knuckles.
并且不要忘记
关于指关节。
And make sure those palms
are squeaky clean.
并确保那些手掌
非常干净。
All right,
let's see those hands.
好吧，
让我们看看那些手。
Now, that's thorough!
现在，彻底了！
After making sure
your feet are polished,
确定后
你的脚被磨光了，
your face is clear
of any blemishes or boils,
你的脸很清晰
任何瑕疵或疖子，
and your hair is neat and tidy,
而且你的头发干净整洁，
you are ready to start the day.
你已经准备好开始新的一天了。
Now let's see how Squidward
prepares for his shift.
现在让我们看看章鱼哥是如何
为他的轮班做准备。
Huh?
啊？
Remember, no employee
wants to be a Squidward.
请记住，没有员工
想成为章鱼哥。
Now that you're clean
and hygienic,
现在你干净了
并且卫生，
I'll bet you think you're ready
to make that Krabby Patty.
我敢打赌你认为你已经准备好了
制作蟹肉饼。
I'm ready!
我准备好了！
Whoa, there.
哇，在那里。
We still have a few more topics
to cover first.
我们还有几个话题
首先覆盖。
It's important to keep your area
tidy and free of droppings.
保留您的区域很重要
整洁且无粪便。
But a clean workstation
is only part of the job.
但有一个干净的工作站
这只是工作的一部分。
To make the vision in your head
a reality, you'll need supplies,
让愿景出现在你的脑海中
事实上，你需要物资，
and a good employee always keeps
his supplies well-organized.
一个好的员工总是会保持
他的物资整理得井井有条。
Very nice, Mr. SquarePants,
not a pickle out of place.
非常好，方裤先生，
不是一个不合适的泡菜。
Now let's see how Squidward
keeps his workstation.
现在让我们看看章鱼哥是如何
保留他的工作站。
Oh!
哦！
Don't worry, Squidward,
别担心，章鱼哥
Mr. SquarePants
can cover for you.
方裤先生
可以为你掩护。
Now that your workstation is up
and running, perhaps you think
现在您的工作站已启动
和跑步，也许你认为
you're ready to make
the world-famous Krabby Patty.
你准备好了
举世闻名的蟹黄饼。
Calm down.
冷静下来。
There's plenty of time left.
还剩很多时间。
We have to make sure
you're ready
我们必须确保
你准备好了
for the psychological aspect
of the job...
对于心理方面
工作的...
Mr. Krabs, can I
have a raise?
蟹老板，我可以吗？
有加薪吗？
No.
不。
Good job, Mr. SquarePants!
干得好，方裤先生！
Can I make a Krabby Patty now?
我现在可以做蟹黄饼吗？
And now we move
from behind the scenes
现在我们搬家了
从幕后
to the front lines,
where we'll examine
到前线，
我们将在哪里检查
the most important aspect
of the industry: the customer.
最重要的方面
行业的本质：客户。
Or, as we like to say,
the "Krustomer."
或者，正如我们喜欢说的，
“克鲁斯托默”。
Who said that?
谁说的？
Are you a ghost?
你是鬼吗？
Like precious,
precious blood in an animal,
如同珍贵的，
动物的宝贵血液，
customers are what keeps The
Krusty Krab strong and alive.
客户是我们的基石
蟹堡王坚强而有活力。
Squidward, your ceiling
is talking to me!
章鱼哥，你的天花板
正在跟我说话！
Are you going to order something
你要订购一些东西吗
or just make friends
with the paneling?
或者只是交朋友
与镶板？
Uh... I'll have an uh...
呃……我要一个呃……
Uh... uh... uh... ah...
呃……呃……呃……啊……
What's that?
那是什么？
Patrick, go be stupid
somewhere else.
帕特里克，去傻吧
其他地方。
Ah-ah-ah, Squidward,
remember what Mr. Krabs says.
啊啊啊啊章鱼哥
记住蟹老板说的话。
The ceiling is right, Squidward,
天花板是对的，章鱼哥，
you're not a very good employee.
你不是一个很好的员工。
Fine.
美好的。
May I please take your order?
我可以接受您的订单吗？
I'll have, uh...
我会有，呃...
Ah...
啊...
We'll check in
with these two later.
我们将办理入住手续
以后和这两个一起。
Right now, it's important
that we discuss an:
现在，很重要
我们讨论：
Like the lost gold of Atlantis,
就像亚特兰蒂斯失落的黄金一样，
many consider their Krabby Patty
to be a treasure.
许多人认为他们的蟹肉饼
成为一个宝藏。
And as with every treasure,
和每一件宝藏一样，
there's a thief
ready to steal it.
有一个小偷
准备偷走它。
So it's up to you
to be the watchful eyes of...
所以这取决于你
成为...的警惕之眼
What's this?
这是什么？
It's Mr. Krabs'
business rival, Plankton.
这是蟹老板的
商业竞争对手，浮游生物。
Eat my microscopic dust, Krabs!
蟹蟹们，吃掉我的微尘吧！
Your secret formula
is finally mine!
你的秘密配方
终于是我的了！
He's stealing the formula!
他偷了配方！
What are you going to do,
Mr. SquarePants?
你要做什么，
方裤先生？
You'll never catch me, Krabs,
你永远抓不到我，蟹蟹，
not when I shift into
maximum overdrive!
不是当我转入
最大超速！
Hi-ya!
嗨呀！
I knew I should've
gotten the turbo.
我知道我应该
得到了涡轮。
Hear me, Krabs!
听我说，蟹蟹们！
You'll take this
Krabby Patty from me
你会拿着这个
来自我的蟹黄派蒂
when you pry it
from my cold, dead...
当你撬开它时
从我的寒冷中，死了......
And so another emergency
is avoided,
于是又发生了一次紧急情况
被避免，
thanks to Mr. SquarePants.
感谢方裤先生。
Let's check in
on Squidward again.
让我们检查一下
再次关于章鱼哥。
Uh...
呃...
Psst, Squidward.
嘘，章鱼哥。
Huh?
啊？
Just remember:
只要记住：
Patrick, if I could
make a suggestion,
帕特里克，如果我可以的话
提出建议，
why don't you just
order a Krabby Patty?
你为什么不直接
点一份蟹肉饼？
Great idea, Squidward.
好主意，章鱼哥。
One Krabby Patty, please.
请来一份蟹肉饼。
Is that for here or to go?
是来这里还是去？
Uh...
呃...
Hang in there, Squidward,
it's all part of the job.
坚持住，章鱼哥，
这都是工作的一部分。
Now that we've covered
all the basics of your training,
现在我们已经介绍了
您训练的所有基础知识，
it's time for the moment
you've been waiting for.
现在是时候了
你一直在等待。
Preparing the Krabby Patty!
准备蟹肉饼！
At the center of every great
dynasty is the crown jewel,
在每一个伟大的中心
王朝是皇冠上的明珠，
which keeps it alive
and thriving.
这使它保持活力
并蓬勃发展。
For The Krusty Krab,
this is the Krabby Patty.
对于蟹堡王来说，
这是蟹黄饼。
And now you, the humble employee
off the street,
现在你，这个卑微的员工
离开街道，
the all-too-necessary
human resource
太必要的
人力资源
that keeps this business afloat,
使这项业务得以维持，
will learn the sacred
and dark secrets
将学习神圣的
和黑暗的秘密
of how to prepare,
with your very own hands...
如何准备，
用你自己的双手...
The sumptuous, lip-moistening,
华丽、润唇、
spine-tingling, heart-stopping
pleasure center
让人脊背发麻、心跳停止
游乐中心
that is a Krabby Patty.
那是蟹肉饼。
Are you ready?
你准备好了吗？
Are you sure?
你确定吗？
Okay, the secret formula...
好吧，秘密公式...
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org